const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following bacteria causes botulism?","answers":[{"option":"Clostridium botulinum","bool":true},{"option":"Clostridium tetani","bool":false},{"option":"Clostridium perfringens","bool":false},{"option":"Clostridium difficile","bool":false},{"option":"Clostridium septicum","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following structures pass through the saphenous opening?","answers":[{"option":"Small saphenous vein and its tributaries","bool":false},{"option":"Great saphenous vein","bool":true},{"option":"Femoral nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Femoral vein","bool":false},{"option":"Superficial inguinal lymph node","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following arteries gives rise to the nutrient artery of the fibula?","answers":[{"option":"Anterior tibial artery","bool":false},{"option":"Popliteal artery","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior medial genicular artery","bool":false},{"option":"Posterior tibial artery","bool":false},{"option":"Peroneal artery","bool":true}]},{"id":3,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles pass through the greater sciatic foramen?","answers":[{"option":"Superior and inferior gemelli","bool":false},{"option":"Piriformis","bool":true},{"option":"Obturator externus","bool":false},{"option":"Quadratus femoris","bool":false},{"option":"Obturator internus","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"What are the contents of the femoral sheath from the lateral to the medial side?","answers":[{"option":"Femoral artery, femoral vein, and the lymphatic vessels","bool":true},{"option":"Femoral vein, femoral artery, and the femoral nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Femoral nerve, femoral artery, and the femoral vein","bool":false},{"option":"Femoral nerve, femoral artery, femoral vein, and the inguinal lymph nodes","bool":false},{"option":"Femoral vein, femoral artery, and the lymphatic vessels","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following structures are present in the femoral canal?","answers":[{"option":"Femoral nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Femoral artery","bool":false},{"option":"Lymphatic vessels and sometimes deep inguinal lymph nodes","bool":true},{"option":"Femoral artery, vein, and the lymphatic vessels","bool":false},{"option":"Femoral vein","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"The femoral sheath is formed by which of the following layers of fascia?","answers":[{"option":"The fascia iliaca and fascia transversalis","bool":true},{"option":"The fascia lata and the membranous layer of the superficial fascia","bool":false},{"option":"The psoas fascia and the fatty layer of the superficial fascia","bool":false},{"option":"the pectineus fascia","bool":false},{"option":"The processes vaginalis","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is the longest muscle in the human body?","answers":[{"option":"Psoas major","bool":false},{"option":"Vastus medialis","bool":false},{"option":"Iliacus","bool":false},{"option":"Pectineus","bool":false},{"option":"Sartorius","bool":true}]},{"id":8,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles is not a part of the hamstring group?","answers":[{"option":"Semimembranosus","bool":false},{"option":"Hamstring portion of adductor magnus","bool":false},{"option":"Short head of biceps femoris","bool":true},{"option":"Semitendinosus","bool":false},{"option":"Long head of biceps femoris","bool":false}]},{"id":9,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"At the postsynaptic membrane in the neuromuscular junction, action potentials are transmitted from axons to muscle fibers by the binding of acetylcholine to its receptor. Which of the following channels open as a result of this binding?","answers":[{"option":"Mg⁺² channels","bool":false},{"option":"Ryanodine channels","bool":false},{"option":"Na⁺ channels","bool":true},{"option":"Dihydropyridine channels","bool":false},{"option":"K⁺ channels","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following types of cells do Howship's lacunae contain?","answers":[{"option":"Osteoblasts","bool":false},{"option":"Osteoclasts","bool":true},{"option":"Osteoprogenitor cells","bool":false},{"option":"Osteocytes","bool":false},{"option":"Chondrocytes","bool":false}]},{"id":11,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is incorrect regarding the lamellae of bone?","answers":[{"option":"Osteoblasts lie in between the lamellae","bool":false},{"option":"Osteoclasts lie within lacunae","bool":false},{"option":"Osteoblasts lie within the lamellae","bool":true},{"option":"Lamellae of woven bone are irregular","bool":false},{"option":"Lamellae are parallel to each other","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following pair of joints is involved in the inversion and eversion of the foot?","answers":[{"option":"Subtalar and talocrural joint","bool":false},{"option":"Subtalar and transverse tarsal joint","bool":true},{"option":"Transverse tarsal and tibiotalar joint","bool":false},{"option":"Talotibial and talocalcanial","bool":false},{"option":"Talocrural and talocalcanial joint","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is the keystone of the medial longitudinal arch of the foot?","answers":[{"option":"Calcaneal tubercle","bool":false},{"option":"Talus head","bool":true},{"option":"Metatarsals","bool":false},{"option":"Navicular bone","bool":false},{"option":"Medial cuneiform bone","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Injury to which of the following nerve causes winging of the scapula?","answers":[{"option":"Nerve to subclavius","bool":false},{"option":"Long thoracic nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Medial pectoral nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral pectoral nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Dorsal scapular nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":15,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is not a part of the anterior compartment of the arm?","answers":[{"option":"Biceps brachii","bool":false},{"option":"Brachial artery","bool":false},{"option":"Radial nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Musculocutaneous nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Coracobrachialis","bool":false}]},{"id":16,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Damage to which pair of nerves is responsible for loss of inversion of the foot?","answers":[{"option":"Deep peroneal and tibial nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Tibial and common peroneal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Superficial and deep peroneal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Superficial peroneal and tibial nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Superficial peroneal and sural nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles is present in the bicipital groove?","answers":[{"option":"Short head of biceps brachii","bool":false},{"option":"Long head of biceps brachii","bool":true},{"option":"Deltoid","bool":false},{"option":"Long head of triceps brachii","bool":false},{"option":"Short head of triceps brachii","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which cofactor is necessary for hydroxylation during collagen synthesis?","answers":[{"option":"Calcitriol","bool":false},{"option":"Ascorbate","bool":true},{"option":"Retinol","bool":false},{"option":"Folate","bool":false},{"option":"Cholecalciferol","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which muscle is most likely to be impaired when a person is unable to flex, abduct, and laterally rotate his thigh?","answers":[{"option":"Sartorius","bool":true},{"option":"Adductor longus","bool":false},{"option":"Obturator externus","bool":false},{"option":"Gracilis","bool":false},{"option":"Gluteus medius","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following arteries does not supply the knee joint?","answers":[{"option":"Anterior tibial artery","bool":false},{"option":"Femoral artery","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral femoral circumflex artery","bool":false},{"option":"Popliteal artery","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior gluteal artery","bool":true}]},{"id":21,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is the most important stabilizer of the shoulder joint?","answers":[{"option":"Rotator cuff muscles","bool":true},{"option":"Trapezius muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Teres major muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Deltoid muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Pectoralis major muscle","bool":false}]},{"id":22,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following amino acids is present at every third position in collagen?","answers":[{"option":"Glutamate","bool":false},{"option":"Hydroxyproline","bool":false},{"option":"Proline","bool":false},{"option":"Glycine","bool":true},{"option":"Lysine","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Extraembryonic mesoderm is present in between which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Extraembryonic membrane and cytotrophoblast","bool":false},{"option":"Syncytiotrophoblast and cytotrophoblast","bool":false},{"option":"Extraembryonic membrane and syncitiotrophoblast","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Exocoelomic membrane and cytotrophoblast","bool":true}]},{"id":24,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"The femoral artery is the continuation of which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"External iliac artery above the inguinal ligament","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":true},{"option":"Internal iliac artery at the level of the inguinal ligament","bool":false},{"option":"External iliac artery at the level of the inguinal ligament","bool":false},{"option":"Internal iliac artery above the inguinal ligament","bool":false}]},{"id":25,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"There are two types of pain, fast and slow pain. The fast type of pain is carried by which of the following fibers?","answers":[{"option":"1B","bool":false},{"option":"A-alpha","bool":false},{"option":"A-beta","bool":false},{"option":"A-delta","bool":true},{"option":"C","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is inappropriate for leflunomide?","answers":[{"option":"Short lifetime","bool":true},{"option":"Prodrug","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Hepatotoxic","bool":false},{"option":"Alopecia","bool":false}]},{"id":27,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following signifies the action of Botulinum toxin?","answers":[{"option":"Blocks the uptake of acetylcholine","bool":false},{"option":"Breaks down the acetylcholine","bool":false},{"option":"Blocks the release of acetylcholine","bool":true},{"option":"Decreases the formation of acetylcholine","bool":false},{"option":"Increases the release of acetylcholine","bool":false}]},{"id":28,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is not a stage for health promotion and education?","answers":[{"option":"Education","bool":false},{"option":"Publicity","bool":false},{"option":"Sensitization","bool":false},{"option":"Legislation","bool":true},{"option":"Community transformation","bool":false}]},{"id":29,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is the largest protein in sarcomere?","answers":[{"option":"Titin","bool":true},{"option":"Myosin","bool":false},{"option":"Tropomodulin","bool":false},{"option":"Actin","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false}]},{"id":30,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"A malignant melanoma (cancer) of the skin covering the buttocks may spread via the lymphatics through which of the following nodes?","answers":[{"option":"Vertical group of superficial inguinal node","bool":false},{"option":"Internal iliac node","bool":false},{"option":"Posterior axillary node","bool":false},{"option":"Horizontal group of superficial inguinal node","bool":true},{"option":"Popliteal node","bool":false}]},{"id":31,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles is involved in the overhead abduction?","answers":[{"option":"Deltoid","bool":false},{"option":"Supraspinatus","bool":false},{"option":"Bicep brachii","bool":false},{"option":"Infraspinatus","bool":false},{"option":"Serratus anterior","bool":true}]},{"id":32,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles is/are found in the trochanteric fossa?","answers":[{"option":"Obturator externus","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Obturator externus, superior gemellus, and inferior gemellus","bool":false},{"option":"Obturator internus, superior gemellus, and inferior gemellus","bool":true},{"option":"Obturator internus","bool":false}]},{"id":33,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"What is the root value of the common peroneal nerve?","answers":[{"option":"S2 to S4","bool":false},{"option":"T2 to T6","bool":false},{"option":"L4 to S2","bool":true},{"option":"S3 to S4","bool":false},{"option":"C2 to C4","bool":false}]},{"id":34,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles holds fractured clavicle in order to prevent damage to the subclavian vein?","answers":[{"option":"Trapezius","bool":false},{"option":"Subclavius","bool":true},{"option":"Deltoid","bool":false},{"option":"Supraspinatus","bool":false},{"option":"Sternocleidomastoid","bool":false}]},{"id":35,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following pertains to the word 'autonomy'?","answers":[{"option":"Work in patient's best interest","bool":false},{"option":"Self rule","bool":true},{"option":"Working with respect to hospital's management","bool":false},{"option":"Equal distribution of medical services","bool":false},{"option":"Do no harm","bool":false}]},{"id":36,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"A patient has suffered a fracture of the surgical neck of the humerus. Which muscle is most likely to be weakened?","answers":[{"option":"Deltoid","bool":true},{"option":"Pectoralis major","bool":false},{"option":"Supraspinatus","bool":false},{"option":"Teres major","bool":false},{"option":"Biceps brachii","bool":false}]},{"id":37,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following proteins is involved in the formation of the cross bridge in the muscle?","answers":[{"option":"Tropomodulin","bool":false},{"option":"Titin","bool":false},{"option":"Myosin","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Actin","bool":false}]},{"id":38,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which vitamin deficiency can cause problems with healing?","answers":[{"option":"Vitamin C","bool":true},{"option":"Vitamin D","bool":false},{"option":"Vitamin E","bool":false},{"option":"Vitamin K","bool":false},{"option":"Vitamin A","bool":false}]},{"id":39,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following substances acts as a vasoconstrictor?","answers":[{"option":"Aspartate","bool":false},{"option":"Dopamine","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Histamine","bool":false},{"option":"Glutamate","bool":false}]},{"id":40,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"According to the sensory classification of nerve fibers, which of the following arise from the annulospiral endings of muscle spindles?","answers":[{"option":"A beta","bool":false},{"option":"A delta","bool":false},{"option":"A gamma","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"A alpha","bool":true}]},{"id":41,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following occurs in acetaminophen overdose?","answers":[{"option":"Status asthmaticus","bool":false},{"option":"Status epilepticus","bool":false},{"option":"Liver failure","bool":true},{"option":"Acute nephropathy","bool":false},{"option":"AV conduction disturbance","bool":false}]},{"id":42,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles is supplied by the common peroneal nerve?","answers":[{"option":"Short head of biceps femoris","bool":true},{"option":"Semitendinous","bool":false},{"option":"Soleus","bool":false},{"option":"Semimembranosus","bool":false},{"option":"Long head of biceps femoris","bool":false}]},{"id":43,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is true regarding rigor mortis?","answers":[{"option":"It occurs before the death","bool":false},{"option":"It is also called instantaneous rigor","bool":false},{"option":"It is the stiffening of body muscles after death","bool":true},{"option":"It occurs 48 hours after death","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":44,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles is the largest muscle of the body?","answers":[{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Gluteus maximus","bool":true},{"option":"Gluteus minimus","bool":false},{"option":"Sartorius","bool":false},{"option":"Gastrocnemius","bool":false}]},{"id":45,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following protein is found in bone?","answers":[{"option":"Type III collagen","bool":false},{"option":"Laminin","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"Fibronectin","bool":false},{"option":"Type I collagen","bool":true}]},{"id":46,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following metacarpals is missing in lobster claw deformity?","answers":[{"option":"2nd","bool":false},{"option":"1st","bool":false},{"option":"5th","bool":false},{"option":"4th","bool":false},{"option":"3rd","bool":true}]},{"id":47,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following investigations is non-ionizing?","answers":[{"option":"X-ray","bool":false},{"option":"Magnetic resonance imaging","bool":true},{"option":"Mammography","bool":false},{"option":"Fluroscopy","bool":false},{"option":"Computed tomography scan","bool":false}]},{"id":48,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is true for smooth muscles?","answers":[{"option":"Calcium binds to calmodulin for contraction","bool":true},{"option":"One type of smooth muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Joined by intercalated discs","bool":false},{"option":"Is in voluntary control","bool":false},{"option":"Works as a syncytium","bool":false}]},{"id":49,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"What happens to the A band of a sarcomere during the contraction of skeletal muscles?","answers":[{"option":"Length decreases","bool":false},{"option":"Length increases","bool":false},{"option":"Move away from one another","bool":false},{"option":"Z discs move away from each other","bool":false},{"option":"Remains the same length","bool":true}]},{"id":50,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"The adductor canal is located in which region of the thigh?","answers":[{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Middle third of thigh","bool":true},{"option":"Lower third of thigh","bool":false},{"option":"Upper third of thigh","bool":false},{"option":"Posterior thigh","bool":false}]},{"id":51,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following options about action potentials in skeletal muscles is correct?","answers":[{"option":"Has an extended plateau phase due to calcium entry","bool":false},{"option":"Occurs when potential is below threshold for activation","bool":false},{"option":"Spontaneously depolarizes via ion channels","bool":false},{"option":"Spread slower than in cardiac muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Spread through transverse tubules","bool":true}]},{"id":52,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"During which period of development does the primary ossification center of the scapula develop?","answers":[{"option":"8 weeks in utero","bool":true},{"option":"At puberty","bool":false},{"option":"During organogenesis","bool":false},{"option":"5 weeks in utero","bool":false},{"option":"At birth","bool":false}]},{"id":53,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"A 60-year-old male presents to the emergency department with a penetrating knife wound to his left gluteal region. After safe removal of the penetrating knife, a physical examination is carried out that reveals a 'waddling gait' characterized by a pelvic drop towards the right side at each step. Which of the following nerves has most likely been damaged as a result of this injury?","answers":[{"option":"Superior gluteal nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Inferior gluteal nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Obturator nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Femoral nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Nerve to obturator internus","bool":false}]},{"id":54,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"A boy was unable to raise his arm above the shoulder level due to damage to a nerve. This nerve supplies which of the following muscles?","answers":[{"option":"Supraspinatus","bool":false},{"option":"Pectoralis major","bool":false},{"option":"Deltoid","bool":false},{"option":"Serratus anterior","bool":true},{"option":"Infraspinatus","bool":false}]},{"id":55,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"What type of joint is the wrist joint?","answers":[{"option":"Pivot joint","bool":false},{"option":"Secondary cartilaginous joint","bool":false},{"option":"Ellipsoidal synovial joint","bool":true},{"option":"Saddle joint","bool":false},{"option":"Hinge joint","bool":false}]},{"id":56,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Where does cartilage originate from?","answers":[{"option":"Epithelium","bool":false},{"option":"Ectoderm","bool":false},{"option":"Proctoderm","bool":false},{"option":"Mesoderm","bool":true},{"option":"Endoderm","bool":false}]},{"id":57,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"In whom is breast cancer more common?","answers":[{"option":"Multiparous women","bool":false},{"option":"Primiparity","bool":false},{"option":"Diabetics","bool":false},{"option":"Grand-Multiparous women","bool":false},{"option":"Nulliparous women","bool":true}]},{"id":58,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles is the primary flexor of the hip joint?","answers":[{"option":"Rectus femoris","bool":false},{"option":"Obturator","bool":false},{"option":"Pectineus","bool":false},{"option":"Psoas major","bool":true},{"option":"Sartorius","bool":false}]},{"id":59,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following helps in the implantation of the blastocyst?","answers":[{"option":"Ectoderm","bool":false},{"option":"Cytotrophoblast","bool":false},{"option":"Syncytiotrophoblast","bool":true},{"option":"Endometrium","bool":false},{"option":"Uterine fluid","bool":false}]},{"id":60,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is the active metabolite of vitamin D?","answers":[{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"25-hydroxyvitamin D3","bool":false},{"option":"7-dehydrocholesterol","bool":false},{"option":"1-hydroxyvitamin D3","bool":false},{"option":"1,25-dihydrocholecalciferol","bool":true}]},{"id":61,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles form the superior boundary of the popliteal fossa?","answers":[{"option":"Biceps femoris, semimembranosus and semitendinosus","bool":true},{"option":"Tendon of bicep femoris and semitendinosus","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"Tricep brachii and semitendinosus","bool":false},{"option":"Semimembranosus and semitendinosus","bool":false}]},{"id":62,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"An improperly placed intramuscular injection at the shoulder region can damage which of the following nerves?","answers":[{"option":"Radial","bool":false},{"option":"Ulnar","bool":false},{"option":"Subscapular","bool":false},{"option":"Thoracodorsal","bool":false},{"option":"Axillary","bool":true}]},{"id":63,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following muscles is not supplied by the musculocutaneous nerve?","answers":[{"option":"Triceps","bool":true},{"option":"Biceps brachii","bool":false},{"option":"None of them","bool":false},{"option":"Brachialis","bool":false},{"option":"Coracobrachialis","bool":false}]},{"id":64,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which artery pierces the adductor magnus and becomes part of cruciate anastomosis?","answers":[{"option":"Profunda femoris artery","bool":false},{"option":"2nd perforating artery","bool":false},{"option":"3rd perforating artery","bool":false},{"option":"1st perforating artery","bool":true},{"option":"Femoral artery","bool":false}]},{"id":65,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"A barium swallow is typically used to examine which of the following organs?","answers":[{"option":"Stomach","bool":false},{"option":"Esophagus","bool":true},{"option":"Small bowel","bool":false},{"option":"Duodenum","bool":false},{"option":"Large bowel","bool":false}]},{"id":66,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is the fourth rule of medical ethics?","answers":[{"option":"Autonomy","bool":false},{"option":"Non-maleficence","bool":false},{"option":"None of them","bool":false},{"option":"Justice","bool":true},{"option":"Beneficence","bool":false}]},{"id":67,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is responsible for the exocytosis of acetylcholine vesicles?","answers":[{"option":"Magnesium","bool":false},{"option":"Potassium","bool":false},{"option":"Chloride","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium","bool":true},{"option":"Sodium","bool":false}]},{"id":68,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which muscle is not innervated by the femoral nerve?","answers":[{"option":"Sartorius","bool":false},{"option":"Vastus lateralis","bool":false},{"option":"Pectineus","bool":false},{"option":"Iliacus","bool":false},{"option":"Gracilis","bool":true}]},{"id":69,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following fractures is more common in sportsmen?","answers":[{"option":"Closed","bool":false},{"option":"Open","bool":false},{"option":"None of them","bool":false},{"option":"Hairline","bool":false},{"option":"Stress","bool":true}]},{"id":70,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Lunate does not articulate with which of the following bones?","answers":[{"option":"Capitate","bool":false},{"option":"Hamate","bool":false},{"option":"Pisiform","bool":true},{"option":"Radius","bool":false},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":71,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"What is the shape of the lunate bone?","answers":[{"option":"Crooked","bool":false},{"option":"Square","bool":false},{"option":"Boat shape","bool":false},{"option":"Semilunar","bool":true},{"option":"Circle","bool":false}]},{"id":72,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"A 20-year-old man suffers from a medial nerve injury. Which of the following methods can confirm this diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Electrocardiogram","bool":false},{"option":"Nerve conduction velocity test","bool":true},{"option":"X-ray","bool":false},{"option":"Muscle biopsy","bool":false},{"option":"Ultrasound","bool":false}]},{"id":73,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following arteries is not injured during the dislocation of the hip joint?","answers":[{"option":"First perforating artery","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Medial circumflex femoral artery","bool":false},{"option":"Lateral circumflex femoral artery","bool":false},{"option":"Inferior and superior gluteal artery","bool":false}]},{"id":74,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following terms refers to decreased bone mass?","answers":[{"option":"Paget's disease","bool":false},{"option":"Osteopenia","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false},{"option":"Osteomalacia","bool":false},{"option":"Osteoporosis","bool":false}]},{"id":75,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following results in a decrease in vitamin D levels?","answers":[{"option":"Induction of 25 hydroxylase in kidney","bool":false},{"option":"Induction of 24 hydroxylase in kidney","bool":false},{"option":"Reduction of 12 hydroxylase in kidney","bool":false},{"option":"Reduction of 1 hydroxylase and induction of 24 hydroxylase in kidney","bool":true},{"option":"None of these","bool":false}]},{"id":76,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which bone is affected when acetabulum is fractured posterosuperiorly?","answers":[{"option":"Ilium","bool":true},{"option":"Ischium","bool":false},{"option":"Pubis","bool":false},{"option":"All of these","bool":false},{"option":"Femoral head","bool":false}]},{"id":77,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is an unmyelinated nerve fiber?","answers":[{"option":"A beta","bool":false},{"option":"A gamma","bool":false},{"option":"C","bool":true},{"option":"A delta","bool":false},{"option":"A alpha","bool":false}]},{"id":78,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following comprises the major organic component of the bone matrix?","answers":[{"option":"Osteoblasts","bool":false},{"option":"Collagen","bool":true},{"option":"Proteoglycans","bool":false},{"option":"Hydroxyapatite crystals","bool":false},{"option":"Calcium phosphate","bool":false}]},{"id":79,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following X-ray views are used to view a fracture?","answers":[{"option":"Anteroposterior and oblique","bool":false},{"option":"Posteroanterior and oblique","bool":false},{"option":"Anteroposterior and lateral","bool":true},{"option":"Oblique and lateral","bool":false},{"option":"Posteroanterior and lateral","bool":false}]},{"id":80,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following cancers can lead to breast cancer?","answers":[{"option":"Brain cancer","bool":false},{"option":"Lung cancer","bool":false},{"option":"Leukemia","bool":false},{"option":"Cervical cancer","bool":false},{"option":"Ovarian cancer","bool":true}]},{"id":81,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following options best corresponds to the following definition: the potential of an event to result in negative consequences?","answers":[{"option":"Stress","bool":false},{"option":"Harm","bool":false},{"option":"Hazard","bool":true},{"option":"Risk","bool":false},{"option":"Vulnerability","bool":false}]},{"id":82,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"A woman was using her sewing machine when her hand slipped and the machine ran over the first web of the hand near the index finger. Which of the following structures will be damaged in this scenario?","answers":[{"option":"Superficial palmar arch","bool":false},{"option":"Axillary nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Ulnar artery","bool":false},{"option":"Deep palmar arch","bool":false},{"option":"Radialis indicis artery","bool":true}]},{"id":83,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following structures is damaged during a cut to the wrist?","answers":[{"option":"Ulnar nerve","bool":true},{"option":"Recurrent branch of median nerve","bool":false},{"option":"Radial indicis artery","bool":false},{"option":"Brachial artery","bool":false},{"option":"Axillary nerve","bool":false}]},{"id":84,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following is a consequence of excessive calcium intake?","answers":[{"option":"Osteoporosis","bool":false},{"option":"Constipation","bool":true},{"option":"Hypotension","bool":false},{"option":"Tetany","bool":false},{"option":"Diarrhea","bool":false}]},{"id":85,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"A fall onto an outstretched arm leads to difficulty in raising the shoulder and neck pain. Which of the following structures when damaged produces such symptoms?","answers":[{"option":"Scapula","bool":false},{"option":"Clavicle","bool":true},{"option":"Radius","bool":false},{"option":"Acromion","bool":false},{"option":"Ulna","bool":false}]},{"id":86,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"An ulnar artery pulse is felt lateral to which of the following structures?","answers":[{"option":"Flexor carpi radialis","bool":false},{"option":"Abductor policis brevis","bool":false},{"option":"Opponens policis","bool":false},{"option":"Flexor policis brevis","bool":false},{"option":"Flexor carpi ulnaris","bool":true}]},{"id":87,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which area is used to assess for a pulse in order to take a blood pressure reading?","answers":[{"option":"In the jugular notch","bool":false},{"option":"Between the 1st and 2nd intercostal spaces","bool":false},{"option":"Middle cranial fossa","bool":false},{"option":"2.5 cm above cubital fossa","bool":true},{"option":"Below the clavicle","bool":false}]},{"id":88,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Where are acetylcholine receptors found?","answers":[{"option":"Synaptic gutter","bool":false},{"option":"Postsynaptic membrane","bool":true},{"option":"Presynaptic membrane","bool":false},{"option":"Synaptic trough","bool":false},{"option":"Mouth of subneural clefts","bool":false}]},{"id":89,"info":"1st-year/locomotor/2016","question":"Which of the following options refers to the action of acetylcholine nicotinic receptors?","answers":[{"option":"Causes widening of the detrussor muscle","bool":false},{"option":"Cause constriction of the iris","bool":false},{"option":"Cause skeletal muscle contraction","bool":true},{"option":"Increase heart rate","bool":false},{"option":"Decrease gastrointestinal motility","bool":false}]}]
export default arr